Tivinia Tonga

Software Engineer

Personal Info

♠ West Jordan, Utah

(801) 564-7693

www.tivinia.com

github.com/tivytonga

■ tivytonga@hotmail.com

Soft Skills

Leadership

Collaboration

Customer Service

Organization

Scrum Development

Hard Skills

MS Excel / Access

Java / Visual Studio

MySQL

Front-End

HTML / CSS

Bootstrap 3.x / 4.x

Javascript React+ / VUE

jQuery

NodeJS

ExpressJS

MongoDB

Back-End

JSON

Computer Science student with 3 years of professional experience and 4 years of personal projects and development. I enjoy responsive designing and coding aimed towards amazing user experiences. My interests include programming, security, and web development.

Experience

Oct 2018 -Present

Freelance Front-End Development

West Jordan, Utah

 Completed Bootcamps to enhance Bootstrap skills and Modern React with Redux skills

Oct 2017 -Oct 2018

Customer Advocate (Remote)

Sandy, Utah

- Process 25+ clinical requests per hour from nurses/physicians/techs/etc.
- Follow HIPAA guidelines with patient data
- Provide excellent customer service to customers of HCSC

Mar 2015 – Aug 2017

Data Security Analyst

Salt Lake City, Utah

- Independently managed and completed projects that consisted of analyzing data for Tandem Help1 and CPM (Ormis).
- Implemented HIPAA-HITECH, Sarbanes-Oxley (SOX) and PCI security standards and regulations in daily processes of Financial and Clinical Systems.
- Provide excellent customer service to customers of FRC includes control owners and vendors of Intermountain Healthcare
- Put together Process Documentation for many major processes in the Cybersecurity department
- Took on a Project Management role for select Cybersecurity projects in order to determine necessary PKI dashboards

Education

Oct 2018 -July 2019 Western Governors University Computer Science BS Degree

Dec 2009

University of Phoenix

Business Administration AA Degree

Certifications

Jan 2019

CompTIA Project+ Certification

Dec 2018

CIW Certification